msparktrk.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | CAKE

##  Protecting Your Privacy

CAKE uses this site to advertise and market its service, which provide customers with a scalable, feature-rich platform, customized to meet their needs for reporting, publishing, managing and guiding affiliate networking campaigns as well as lead distribution.

CAKE is also committed to protecting the privacy of our users. To this end, we believe you have the right to know everything regarding the information we collect about you, how the information is used, and how you can opt out of providing any of this information.

This privacy policy explains how we use your information and explains what you can expect from CAKE. By using this site, you indicate your acceptance of CAKE’s Privacy Policy.

###  What Information Is Collected?

We collect personally identifying information from voluntary user registrations, requests for information, surveys, contact forms and emails. We also collect non-personally identifying information when you visit our website about which pages you visit, how long you visit certain pages, and how you arrived at our website among other things. For more information on exactly what information is obtained, please contact us at [privacy@getCAKE](mailto:privacy@getCAKE).

###  Why Do You Collect Information?

The information we collect allows us to improve your user experience through the customization of content and layouts of various pages. It also enables us to respond to your requests for information and keep you informed about new features and services that we offer along with any content that we provide through our newsletters. In addition, some information is shared with reputable organizations who may contact you with special offers of possible interest.

We may use your personal information with non-personal information that we have collected in a manner such that the end-product does not personally identify you or any other user of our site.  We may make your personal information non-personally identifiable by either combining it with information about other users (aggregating your personal information with information about other users), or by removing characteristics (such as your name or email address) that make the information personally identifiable.  This process is known as de-personalizing your information.  You grant us a royalty-free, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable and fully transferable right and license to use your personal information in connection with the creation and development of analytical and statistical analysis tools relating to the use of the customer data we collect in providing the site and our services (the “Analytical Data”). We are expressly authorized to make any commercial use of the Analytical Data, including without limitation, sharing the Analytical Data with third parties, provided that we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer from us any part of the Analytical Data that personally identifies any of our website users.

###  Who Do You Share My Information With?

We may make our customer e-mail addresses, postal addresses and telephone numbers available to other reputable businesses whose products or services may be of value to you. If you do not wish to share your information with other companies or organizations, please let us know by contacting us at [privacy@getCAKE.com](mailto:privacy@getCAKE.com), by calling us at 424-238-5976, or writing to us at Customer Service, CAKE, Inc., 2244 W Coast Hwy Suite 250, Newport Beach, CA 92663. We retain email opt-out and postal/telephone non-solicitation requests for five years.

###  May I see the Information You Collect From Me?

Yes, upon request, we will provide you with access to your personal account information, account status, contact information, and other information that we collect. You may access the information by emailing us a request at [privacy@getCAKE.com](mailto:privacy@getCAKE.com).

We also allow visitors to correct any inaccuracies in their contact information simply by emailing the changes to us at [privacy@getCAKE.com](mailto:privacy@getCAKE.com).

###  What Are Cookies?

We may use cookies to store your individual user preferences in order to make your user experience more enjoyable in the future. Cookies are tiny bits of information stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Most browsers are initially setup to accept cookies by default and they are commonly found on many websites throughout the Internet.

If you wish to disable cookies, there is a simple procedure in most Internet browsers that allow you to turn off cookies. However, note that cookies may be required to use certain features of our website and that of many others.

We may also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (non-personally identifying) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and become aware of your choice to not have this information used by companies, please contact us at [privacy@getCAKE.com](mailto:privacy@getCAKE.com).

###  Legal Information Transfers

We may need to disclose certain information to comply with laws, regulations, court orders, subpoenas, search warrants, or other legal reasons in the course of a legal proceeding or in response to a law enforcement agency request. Furthermore, if there is a change of control transaction in our business, a sale or transfer of assets, customer information could be sold or transferred as part of that transaction and your personally identifying information may be used by the purchaser.  We may also share your personal information with service providers that we engage for the purpose of processing information on our and your behalf.  For example, we may partner with other companies to process, analyze, and/or store data, including, but not limited to, Analytical Data.  While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information.  To the extent applicable, we require these entities to comply with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

###  Children Under 13

We are concerned about the safety of children. We do not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 13 to provide us with personally identifying information. Children wishing to utilize our services should always get permission from their parents before supplying any information about themselves, including names, email addresses and phone numbers.

###  Hyperlinks

We may link to other websites with information gathering practices that differ from our own. Visitors should carefully review privacy policies for all websites they visit as we have no control over information submitted or collected by third parties.

We may also offer contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions from time to time that are sponsored or co-sponsored by third parties. These third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstake or promotion. We have no control over how these third parties use this information; however, we will notify you whenever you fill out a form that will provide them access to such information.

###  CAKE Newsletter and Opt Out Procedure

The CAKE Newsletter is provided to customers and any other interested parties as a resource for information related to product upgrades, special announcements, and other company and industry news.  When you enter your email address on getCAKE.com you are agreeing to accept emails from us until you decide to opt out of the program.

If you do not want to receive email from us, please use the unsubscribe option available on email communications, or by emailing us at [](mailto:privacy@getCAKE.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Inquiry)[privacy@getCAKE.com](mailto:privacy@getCAKE.com), by calling us at 949-548-CAKE, or by writing to us at Customer Service, CAKE, Inc. 2244 W Coast Hwy Suite 250, Newport Beach, CA 92663. We will retain all such email opt-out requests for five years.

###  You agree not to use our website in order to:

  * perform any commercial activities without the written consent of CAKE
  * forge headers or manipulate identifiers as a means to mask the origin of any content transmitted through the Service;
  * disrupt the servers or networks connected to the CAKE site;
  * transmit any content, materials or submissions that is unlawful, invasive of another's privacy, or otherwise objectionable;
  * hurt minors in any way, “stalk” any individuals or gather personal information about other users;
  * pretend to be any person or entity or feign your affiliation with a person or entity;
  * transmit any content, materials or submissions that would infringe upon another’s intellectual property rights or would be considered “spam”, “chain letters” or any other form of solicitation;
  * post any content, materials or submissions that you should not transmit under any contract, law or fiduciary relationship or any content, materials or submissions containing any viruses or programs that would effect functionality;
  * develop password-only, restricted access pages, or hidden pages;
  * break any applicable laws or regulations or aid any other user in achieving illegal activities.

###  How Is Data Secured?

We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving personal data. We also have appropriate security measures to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of information that we collect from you.

###  Changes and Updates

We may need to change this privacy policy from time to time in order to address new issues, new technologies, changes in our website or business practices. We will always post these changes so you will know what information we gather and how we may use that information. Please consult this policy regularly for such updates.

###  Members’ Rights

By using this website, you acknowledge that we acquire all rights to use any submitted materials as described above so that we do not violate any rights you may have in materials you submit. By submitting content to or throughout our website, you grant us the non-exclusive right to reproduce, modify and distribute it as we see fit in any medium and for any propose in any form, media or technology now known or later developed. You also permit any other user to access, display and print such content for personal use. You vouch that any material you submit does not violate, plagiarize or infringe upon the right of any third party, including copyright, trademark or proprietary rights. If non-original content is included in your posting, you much obtain permission from the content owner and attribute it.

###  Mediation

If you are a resident of a country outside of the European Union, you also agree that, in the event any dispute or claim arises out of or relating to this Privacy Policy that you and CAKE will attempt in good faith to negotiate a written resolution of the matter directly between the parties.  You agree that if the matter remains unresolved for forty-five (45) days after notification (via certified mail or personal delivery) that a dispute exists, all parties shall join in mediation services in Orange County, California with a mutually agreed mediator in an attempt to resolve the dispute.  Should you file any arbitration claims, or any administrative or legal actions without first having attempted to resolve the matter by mediation, then you agree that you will not be entitled to recover attorneys’ fees, even if you would otherwise be entitled to them.

###  Dispute Resolution for Residents of the European Union

If you are a resident of the European Union, in the event that you have any dispute or claim arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, you may report your claim to the European Union Data Protection Authorities located in your jurisdiction. 

###  Special Note to Users Outside of the United States

Our site is hosted in the United States. If you are a user accessing our site from the European Union or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of our site, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you hereby consent to the transfer of such information outside of the country where you are located.

###  European Commission’s Directive on Data Protection - Safe Harbor

CAKE adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles that were established by the U.S. Department of Commerce in consultation with the European Commission to comply with the European Commission’s Directive on Data Protection.  For more information, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor>.

###  Further Questions or Comments

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or feel that his website has not followed its stated privacy policy, feel free to contact us by email at [privacy@getCAKE.com](mailto:privacy@getCAKE.com), by phone at 424-238-5976, or by mail at Customer Service, CAKE, Inc. 2244 W Coast Hwy Suite 250, Newport Beach, CA 92663 Note: This privacy policy applies to all of CAKE’s owned and operated websites and to CAKE’s other information gathering activities.
